[
  [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "59 + 95",
      "answer": 154,
      "wrong_answers": [54, 102, 112]
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "313 x 5",
      "answer": 1565,
      "wrong_answers": [1315, 1535, 1554]
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "376 - 1",
      "answer": 375,
      "wrong_answers": [275, 323, 333]
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "304 x 79",
      "answer": 24016,
      "wrong_answers": [23766, 23986, 24005]
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "116 - 79",
      "answer": 37,
      "wrong_answers": [36, 32, -13]
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "364 - 27",
      "answer": 337,
      "wrong_answers": [237, 285, 295]
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "167 + 65",
      "answer": 232,
      "wrong_answers": [132, 180, 190]
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "42 - 49",
      "answer": -7,
      "wrong_answers": [-8, -12, -57]
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "383 + 39",
      "answer": 422,
      "wrong_answers": [322, 370, 380]
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "72 x 67",
      "answer": 4824,
      "wrong_answers": [4574, 4794, 4813]
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "171 - 21",
      "answer": 150,
      "wrong_answers": [50, 98, 108]
    },
    {
      "id": "12",
      "question": "52 - 25",
      "answer": 27,
      "wrong_answers": [26, 22, -23]
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "229 - 37",
      "answer": 192,
      "wrong_answers": [92, 140, 150]
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "5 - 87",
      "answer": -82,
      "wrong_answers": [-83, -87, -132]
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "61 x 1",
      "answer": 61,
      "wrong_answers": [60, 56, 11]
    },
    {
      "id": "16",
      "question": "177 + 5",
      "answer": 182,
      "wrong_answers": [82, 130, 140]
    }
  ]
]
